- 好吧   - 过来 不能偷看喔
- Okay.         - Come on, no peeking.
我们要闭眼睛过马路 太好了
Our eyes are closed, and we're about to cross the street. Very good.
好 可以看了
Okay. Open up.
你们是要我们看什么？因为我只看到超炫的厢型车
What do you want to show us? Because all I can see is this bitchen van.
这是我们做外烩的专用车
Yeah, it's for our catering business.
- 噢   - 我好像认识那女孩
- Oh.     - I think I know that girl.
- 好吧 但最后不会是这样   - 不会吗？
- We're not gonna keep it this way, though.     - No?
我们会把宝刀换成法国面包
We're gonna paint over the sword and replace it with a baguette.
噢
Oh.
还有这个也不知道要怎么处理
Um, also, we don't know what to do with this.
对 我一定认识她
Oh, yeah, I definitely know her.
还记得我说过那梱在烹饪学校 煮什么都加香菜的人吗？
Remember that guy from cooking school that put cilantro in everything?
- 记得 香菜赖瑞嘛   - 记得
- Oh, sure, Cilantro Larry.     - Yeah.
我要替他代班 帮《赤尔夕通讯报》做美食评监
Well, I'm gonna fill in for him as food critic for the Chelsea Reporter.
哇 摩妮卡 这可是大好机会呢 你能影响到…
Wow. Monica, what an amazing opportunity to influence...
二 三十个人呢
...dozens of people.
那我们的外烩生意怎么办？
What about our catering business?
我这个一星期只要一个晚上
Oh, no, no, it's just one night a week.
我还能带你们到处去吃免钱的
Plus, I get to take all of you out for free dinners.
- 嘿   - 噢
- Hey.     - Oh.
既然是那样的话…
Well, in that case:
- 刚才是我跳上车一起去   - 噢
- That was me hopping onboard.     - Oh.
大伙儿好 罗斯？快问快答
Hey, guys. Hey, Ross. Quick question for you.
你准备好要狂欢没？
Are you ready to party?
没有 出去喝几杯啤酒或许行
I don't know, I could maybe go out for a couple of beers.
但是今晚发现频道要演大黄峰
But there's this thing about bumblebees on the Discovery Channel.
你可能没听清楚 你准备好要狂欢没？
No, no, no, I don't think you heard me. Are you ready to party?
不会吧
No.
甘道夫… 甘道夫要来？
Gandalf? Gandalf is coming to town?
凯西去找她父母 我没事干
Kathy's with her parents, I have nothing to do.
明天我们去跟甘道夫狂欢吧 兄弟
Tomorrow we are partying with Gandalf, dude.
兄弟 我们要去狂欢了耶
Dude, we are so gonna party. Yeah.
好吧 兄弟请注意
Wow, okay. Dude alert.
这个人是谁？
And who is this guy?
麦克甘道夫甘德森 世界上最爆笑的人
Mike "Gandalf" Ganderson. Only, like, the funnest guy in the world.
我要打给公司说明天请假
I'm gonna call and get off work tomorrow.
你打完换我
Oh. I'm gonna call after you.
兄弟 这一定超酷的 我们八百年没狂欢了
This is gonna be so cool. Dude, we never party anymore.
哇
Whoo!
你们是不是躲在厢型车里 偷抽了大麻？
All right, were you guys smoking something in the back of our van?
是啊 什么叫八百年没狂欢 跟我在一起就很乐啊
What do you mean, we never have fun? You have fun with me.
记得去看脱衣舞那回？你们给我50美元要我吞书
Remember the time we saw those strippers and you paid me 50 bucks to eat that book?
乔伊 这个人你一定会喜欢 甘道夫是狂欢巫师喔
Joey, you are gonna love this guy. Gandalf is like the party wizard.
- 你们干嘛叫他"甘道夫"？ - 巫师甘道夫啊
- Well, why do you call him Gandalf?     - Gandalf the wizard.
你念高中没看过《魔戒》吗？
Hello? Didn't you read Lord of the Rings in high school?
没 但我念高中有上过床
No, I had sex in high school.
乔安娜 我有件事想请问一下
Oh. Uh, Joanna? I was wondering if I could ask you something.
少淑女服饰的采购助理有空缺
There's an opening for an assistant buyer in Junior Miss...
那我岂不是连降三级了？
Okay, but that would be a step down for me.
不是啦 我是毛遂自荐
No, actually, I meant for me.
招聘委员会每天都在面试…
The hiring committee is meeting people all day and...
我很希望我能拒绝 但总不能让你永远当我助理吧
Oh. Well, I wish I could say no, but I guess you can't stay my assistant forever.
苏菲 你也是 但理由不同
Neither can you, Sophie, but for different reasons.
真高兴你完全没有意见
I'm so glad you don't have a problem with this.
否则我压根不会想去报考
If you did, I wouldn't have considered applying.
真的啊 那样的话…
Really? In that case...
所以我才很高兴你没意见
And that's why I'm so glad there's no problem.
没关系 其实我也是面试人员之一 你起码能看到一张友善的脸
Yeah, it's fine. I'm on the hiring committee, so there'll be one friendly face.
这真是太棒了
Oh, that's great.
- 我也是从少淑女部起家的   - 真的吗
- You know, Junior Miss is where I started.     - Really?
跟个一级丑男上床 才得到那份工作
I had to sleep with the ugliest guy to get that job.
- 真的啊？ - 才不呢
- Really?     - No. Ha, ha.
是真的
Yeah.
- 话说回来…   - 没有啦
- I mean, no. No, no, no. Ha, ha.     - No. Ha, ha.
别担心 以你的资历 不用出卖肉体也能被录取
I'm sure with your qualifications, you won't need to sleep with some guy.
哈哈
Oh. Ha, ha.
虽然我可能要验货确定一下
Although, uh, I might need some convincing.
- 噢…   - 逗你的啦
- Um... Oh.     - Kidding. Ha, ha.
- 天啊 我今天真兴奋   - 哈哈
- God, I feel wild today.     - Aah!
要命 我兴奋到都快吐了
Oh, man, I am so excited, I may vomit.
你兴奋个什么劲？他不过就是个人嘛
Will you calm down? He's just a human guy.
你有所不知 甘道夫超神的
Look, you don't understand. Gandalf is amazing.
跟他出去可是惊喜连连
You never know what's gonna happen.
几杯啤酒下肚 醒来竟然正在坐渔船去加拿大
You go out for a couple of beers and end up on a fishing boat to Nova Scotia.
- 真的？ - 对 那里风景很美
- Really?     - Oh, yeah, it's beautiful country up there.
好
Hey. Okay.
我带了护照 干净的袜子 还有蛇毒解药
I got my passport, fresh socks, and a snakebite kit.
这次不会跟上次完全一样啦
It's not gonna be exactly like last time.
回头见了
All right, I'll see you guys.
等等…
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我要先去试镜 晚点一定去跟你们会合
I have an audition, but I'll hook up with you later.
- 你们中午左右会在哪里？ - 哦
- Where you gonna be around noon?     - Heh.
差不多在赤道附近吧
Somewhere maybe along the equator?
好
Okay.
喂？
Hello?
甘道夫打来的
It's Gandalf.
你已经到了？
So are you in town?
喔 这样啊…
Oh, well...
那就下次再约吧
Well, maybe next time, then.
怎么了？
What happened?
他在芝加哥被耽搁了 没办法来
He's not gonna make it. He's stuck in Chicago.
要命
Oh, man.
芝加哥真是太走运了
Chicago's so lucky.
真是愚蠢又没有用的加拿大币
Stupid, useless Canadian money.
葛林小姐 你的履历非常精彩
You have a very impressive résumé, Ms. Green.
特别是我看到了这一段 "实施档案管理系统"
I especially like what I see here about implementing a new filing system.
谢谢
Thank you.
"档案管理系统"？你说资料夹上黏的彩色标签啊
Filing system? Oh, you mean those little colored labels you put on all the folders?
那的确是让档案柜生色不少
It certainly did brighten up the inside of the filing cabinets.
功能不只是那样而已
Well, they, uh... They did more than that.
我看到你肩负了许多重要职责
I notice that you've been entrusted with a lot of important responsibilities.
对 乔安娜真是我的导师
Yes. Joanna really has been an incredible mentor to me.
瑞秋也是帮我买贝果的贵人
Oh. And Rachel has been really incredible at getting my morning bagel.
不可思议 她几乎每次都不会买错
It's amazing how she gets it right almost every time.
我的职责当然不止那样
Of course, I have more responsibilities than that.
没错 还有咖啡也是 瑞秋一次能拎两样东西
Oh, yes, of course. There's the coffee too. Rachel can carry two things at once.
相当优秀
That's, uh, very good.
这项工作的一大重点是
Now, a big part of this job...
打好人际关系 尤其是和设计师
...is cultivating personal relationships, especially with designers.
- 对 我知道…   - 这一点瑞秋没问题
- Yes, I realize...     - Rachel shouldn't have any problem.
只怕她打得太火热 懂吧？
Her only problem might be getting a little too friendly, if you know what I mean.
我最爱和设计师共事了
I love working with designers.
共事或共枕又有何差别呢？瑞秋
With them, under them, what's the difference, eh, Rach?
我第一篇美食评论上报了
Hey. My first review is out.
《赤尔夕通讯报》
Oh! Oh, the Chelsea Reporter.
以前我都拿这来当棉被盖
Ah. These used to keep me so warm.
- 快看 我写的专刊在反面   - 噢
- All right, look, I'm on the back page.     - Ooh. Oh!
好 "我会再光顾亚历山卓吗？当然 但我会点两份餐
Okay. "Would I go back to Allesandro's? Sure, but I would have to order two meals.
一份给自己一份给拿枪抵着我的人"
One for me, and one for the guy pointing the gun to my head."
哇 你真把这家店批得一文不值
Wow, you really laid into this place.
报社付我钱 可不是要我广结善缘
Hey, they don't pay me a penny a word to make friends.
我得走了 我找到一个人 他能搞定那部外烩厢型车
Ooh, I gotta go. I found a guy who could fix up the van for catering.
- 要我一起去吗？ - 不用了 没关系
- Oh. You want me to go with you?     - No, no, it's okay.
但你确定我们不要那张水床？
But are we sure we don't want the waterbed?
- 我们不是早就说好了？ - 对啦 算了
- Haven't we made this decision?     - Yeah, all right.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Bye.
谁啊？
Who is it?
我是亚历山卓的老板
It's Allesandro, from Allesandro's.
天啊
Oh, my God.
- 我要跟你讨论美食评监的事   - 天啊…
- I wanna talk to you about your review.     - Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
你打电话给我
Call me on the phone.
好让你挂我电话？
What, so you can hang up on me?
我不会让你上来的 你还是走吧
I'm never gonna let you up, so you may as well just go away.
给我一个机会…
Just give me a chance to...
你要进来吗？请进
Do you need to get in? Here you go.
- 菲比 不行啦   - 嗨 摩妮卡
- No, Phoebe!     - Oh, hey, Monica.
我要你收回你的话 我们的食物绝非"难以下咽"
I want a retraction. Our food is not "inedible swill."
我就吃不下去
I couldn't eat it.
我那五个朋友也难以下咽 其中一佃人连书都能吃了
I have five friends who couldn't eat it, and one of them eats books.
我们的服务 也不是宾至如"衰"
Well, our service is not "grossly incompetent."
那侍者把面包棒塞在裤子里
The waiter carried the breadsticks in his pants.
你还写说 我们店里接受发现卡
Well, you said that we accept the Discover Card...
其实不行
...which we do not.
好啊 那段话我可以收回
All right, that I'll retract.
但我扞卫我写的评论 我懂美食 你们的差远了
But I stand by my review. I know food, and that wasn't it.
你们的大蒜番茄酱 简直跟蕃茄汁没两样
Your marinara sauce tastes like tomato juice.
应该要加伏特加和芹菜
You should serve it with vodka and a piece of celery.
我很以店里那酱汁为荣 可口极了
Hey, I'm proud of that sauce. It's delicious.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是开意大利餐厅的 竟然觉得那样叫做可口？
You own an Italian restaurant and you think that tastes good?
你到底是哪里人？
Where are you even from?
黎巴嫩
Lebanon.
把那些蕃茄给我
Hand me those tomatoes.
我来示范纯正的味道是怎样 来 给我
I'm gonna show you what it should taste like. Come on, hand them to me.
你要弄多久？我还要去骂另一个美食评论家
How long is this gonna take? I got another critic I gotta go yell at.
乔安娜 我要谈谈面试的事
Ahem. Uh, Joanna, I wanna talk about that interview.
我觉得你在面试中表现得很棒
I thought it went very well.
不 才怪 我就是要跟你说这件事
No, it didn't. That's what I wanna talk to you about.
我先声明一句…
[IN STRAINED VOICE] Now, just to brief you...
我可能会哭出来
...I may cry.
但那不是悲伤或气愤的泪水
But they are not tears of sadness or of anger...
只是因为我要你跟讨论这件事
...but just of me having this discussion with you.
瑞秋 麻烦你别丢人现眼了
Rachel, please, don't make a scene.
这里又没人
There's nobody here.
苏菲 你进来
Sophie, get in here.
看吧 你让苏菲尴尬了
You see? Now you're making Sophie uncomfortable.
我没有尴尬啊
She's not making me uncomfortable.
恭喜 你刚刚证明了 自己一无是处 滚吧
Congratulations, you've just crossed the line into completely useless. Get out.
你是要我辞职吗？
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Do you want me to quit?
什么？你怎么会这样想？
What? What would make you think that?
因为你在面试时讲的那些话
Well, all of those things you said in the interview.
如果里面有你的真心话 那我一定不是个好助理
If you believe any of them, I must not be a very good assistant.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我要来收拾办公桌
I am just going to pack up my desk...
我等今天下班就走人
...and I will be gone by the end of the day.
我想没必要耗到今天下班了
Well, I guess there's no use me sticking around till the end of the day.
你等等…
Wait, wait, wait.
把那可怜的松糕放回抽屉里
You can put your sad little muffin back in its drawer.
如果你要听实话的话 是我不想失去你这完美的助理
If you must know the truth, I didn't wanna lose a good assistant.
什么？
What?
所以我才瞎办出那些招峰引蝶 还有你酗酒的事
That's why I said all those things about your flirting and your drinking.
我酗酒？
My drinking?
我等你离开之后才说的
Oh. I must have said that after you left.
你到底说了什么？
Said what, exactly?
你三不五时喜欢喝一杯…
That you enjoy the occasional drink...
酒后乱性
...- ing binge.
天啊 真是够了 我走人了
Oh, my God. Oh. That is it. I'm leaving.
- 你这个人真的很糟糕   - 等等…
- You are just a horrible person.     - No, wait, wait, wait.
反应不用那么激烈嘛
Now, if you're gonna get all sensitive about it.
我不想失去你
I don't want to lose you.
不如我变出个职位给你？
What if I create a position for you?
我让你在这个部门里 担任采购助理
I'll make you assistant buyer in this department.
- 你再多说一点   - 呃…
- Say more things like that.     - Um...
你有自己的办公室 外带加薪 明天就生效
You can have your own office and a raise, effective tomorrow.
- 我需要公关费   - 没问题
- I'd need an expense account.     - Done.
- 还要有助理   - 苏菲 进来
- And an assistant.     - Sophie, get in here.
现在感觉像是一辈子 不是吗？从…
Now it seems like a lifetime, doesn't it? Starting from...
你们怎么在这里？
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
不是跟甘呆夫去狂欢了？
I thought you'd be partying with Gandoldorf.
是甘道夫 他不来了
It's Gandalf, and he's not coming.
- 那你们一早都呆坐在这里？ - 没有
- So you've been sitting here all morning?     - No.
我刚刚把帐算好了
I balanced my checkbook.
对 足球台里的选手 我也全都取好了名字
Yeah, and I gave first names to all the foosball players.
不敢相信甘道夫竟然没来
I can't believe he didn't come.
他不来又怎样？我们还是可以自己出去狂欢啊
So what if he didn't come? We can still go out and party ourselves.
有甘道夫在 一整晚都有的玩
Oh, no, you know, with Gandalf, we'd be out all night.
而且能和一堆陌生人一起混
Yeah, we'd meet total strangers and hang out with them.
我们也可以啊
Well, we could do that.
他还有其他的绝招啦
There was other stuff too.
我们一网打尽 更胜于蓝
We'll do it all, and better.
兄弟 今晚过后 就换我们带甘道夫去狂欢
Look, after tonight, Gandalf will wanna party with us, dude.
来吧
Come on.
- 对   - 对
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
- 活像我们不会狂欢似的   - 好 咱们走
- It's not like we don't know how to party.     - Yeah. All right. Let's go.
最后再到一次船上如何？
And maybe we could end up on a boat again?
- 好耶   - 太棒了
- Yeah!     - All right!
哇
Ah!
上次在船上是何时？
Hey, hey, hey. When were we on a boat?
记得那天早上很冷
Remember that really cold morning...
一早醒来还有狗舔你的脸？
...when you woke up and those dogs were licking your face?
- 记得   - 老兄 舔你的可是海豹呢
- Yeah.     - Those were seals, man.
摩妮卡 快问快答 采购助理穿这套装如何？
Hey, how do you think this suit would look on an assistant buyer...?
亚历山卓的老板上门来吼我
The owner of Allesandro's came to yell at me...
但我趁机帮他做了酱料 结果他挖我去店里当主厨
...but I made him some sauce, and he offered me the job as head chef.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你毁了我练的好戏 但我真是替你高兴
You just ruined the thing I was practicing the whole way home, but I'm so happy.
你相信吗？我终于可以在厨房当老大了
Can you believe it? I finally get to run my own kitchen.
你盼了那么久
Oh, you've waited so long.
- 嗨   - 菲比 快问快答
- Hey.     - Hey, Pheebs. Quick question for you.
布鲁明岱尔的采购助理穿上这套装如何？
How do you think this suit would look on an assistant buyer at Bloomingdale's?
那完全要看她的肤色而定
I don't know. It would totally depend on her coloring and...
- 你拿到那工作了   - 是的
- You got the job!     - Yes!
你被录取了？怎么没跟我说？
Oh! You got the job? Why didn't you tell me?
- 一定超棒的 我能帮忙决定要卖什么
Oh. It's gonna be so great. I'm gonna get to help decide what we sell.
还有全套装置和墙的办公室
I'm gonna have an office with walls and everything.
- 四面都有墙耶   - 哇
- I'm gonna have walls.   - Aw.
今天真是喜事连连 我帮我们找到工作了
Is this the day of good news or what? I got us a job.
喜宴外烩
The wedding reception.
噢
Oh.
菲比 我有话要跟你说
Um, Phoebe, I kind of need to talk to you about that.
哦
Um...
我想外烩的事不能操之过急
Well, I think it might be time for me to take a step back from the catering.
- 但我们才做了一笔生意啊   - 啧啧
- But we've only had one job.     - Tsk.
我知道 但现在有第二笔了 就像雪球越滚越大
I know, but now we have this second one, and it just feels like it's snowballing.
你在说什么？
Yeah, what are you saying?
亚历山卓餐厅请我去当主厨
I got offered the head-chef job at Allesandro's.
- 什么？ - 不碍事的 仔细想想 其实你也不需要我
- What?     - It's okay, you don't really need me.
你是厨师耶
You're the cook.
总不能我自己一个开去别人家
Without you, it's just me driving up to people's houses...
带着空盘子就跟人要钱吧？
...with empty trays and asking for money.
好
All right.
我会还回所有你投资的钱
But, um, well, I'll pay you back all the money you invested.
- 而那部厢型车归你   - 我要拿来干嘛？
- And you can keep the van.     - For what?
我真是不敢相信 我得离开这里
I can't believe this. I gotta get out of here.
菲比 你等等
Phoebe, wait a minute.
我升采购助理了
I'm an assistant buyer!
我们先喝咖啡养足精神 再重新出发
All right, we'll get a little coffee, get energized, then we'll head back out.
- 好吧   - 好
- Yeah, all right.     - Okay.
很好玩嘛 对不对？我们才不需要那个什么巫师的
So we're having fun, right? We don't need that wizard guy.
我们去了几家俱乐部 跟一些陌生人说过话
We hit a couple of clubs, talked to some strangers...
等一下去码头安排坐船的事
...then after this, we'll go down to the docks and see about that boat thing.
我有点累了
I'm kind of beat.
其实…
Actually...
我也是
...me too.
你们是真的假的？
Are you serious?
耶
Yeah.
感谢老天 我也累毙了
Thank God. I'm exhausted.
你们要喝咖啡吗？
So you guys want coffees?
对 但我今天想早点睡 所以我要无咖啡因的
Yeah, but I don't wanna be up too late, so I'll have a decaf.
对 我也是
Yeah, me too.
我能来杯热水加点柠檬汁吗？
Actually, could I get some hot water with a little lemon?
我刚才在那家店里都喊到哑了 他们音乐非要开那么大声吗？
I strained my voice screaming in there. Does it have to be so loud?
我听不到你说什么 我耳鸣得厉害
Oh. I can't hear a word you're saying, my ears are ringing so bad.
幸好我多带了一双袜子
Huh. I was glad I brought that extra pair of socks, you know?
拿来当手套用
I used them as mittens.
最后那家店脏到我不敢用手碰
I didn't wanna touch a thing in that last place.
噢
Oh.
我们真是可悲到了极点
How sad are we?
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
其实我们并不可悲
You know what? We're not sad.
只是我们都不再是21岁了
We're not sad, we're just not 21 anymore, you know?
我都已经29岁了
I'm 29 years old, damn it.
只想舒服地坐着看电视
I wanna sit in a comfortable chair, watch television...
时间到了就上床睡觉
...and go to sleep at a reasonable hour.
我喜欢去安静一点的地方 才能好好跟朋友聊天
Yeah, and I like to hang out in a quiet place where I can talk to my friends.
耶
Yeah.
就算回家听肯尼吉的音乐洗澡 又有什么大不了的？
And so what if I like to go home, throw on some Kenny G, and take a bath?
我们是29岁没错 但我们可不是娘儿们
We're 29. We're not women.
你来了
Oh. There you are.
我很高兴你决定听我解释
Hey, I'm glad that you decided to hear me out.
好 你说吧
Okay, I'm hearing.
我想了很多 很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking. A lot.
我想出了你用厢型车 可以做的所有生意
And, well, I came up with a whole bunch of businesses that you can do with your van.
对的 嗯…
Okay, um...
- 你可以去送花   - 什么？
- You could be a flower delivery person.     - What?
或是送面包？
Or a bakery delivery person.
送比萨？
Pizza?
摩妮卡？
Monica.
我写了一堆你能运送的东西
All right, I got a whole bunch of stuff in this area...
但我有预感你不想送货
...but I'm getting the feeling you don't wanna deliver.
- 不想   - 那好吧
- No.     - Okay.
我猜若你不想送货的话…
I'm guessing if you don't wanna deliver...
八成也不会想去取货
...you probably don't wanna pick up stuff either.
对
No.
不如这样吧
You know what?
- 我们来做外烩   - 真的？你确定？
- Let's do the catering business.     - Really? Are you sure?
对 我承诺过你
Yeah. You know, I made a commitment to you.
- 会很有趣的   - 一定会很有趣的
- Know what? Lt'd be fun.     - Oh, it will be fun.
那我们来计划喜宴的事
Okay. Ooh, let's plan the wedding reception. Okay.
好耶
Wow.
你还真的是很用心 想让我用这厢型车来做些事
You really wanted me to do something with this van.
不如这样吧 我要你接下那主厨的工作
You know what? I want you to take the chefjob.
- 真的？ - 对
- Really?     - Yeah.
那是你真心想要做的
That's what you really want.
我不想成为你不高兴的原因
Yeah, I don't wanna be the reason you're unhappy.
那样我也会不高兴
That would make me unhappy.
我更不想让自己不高兴
And I really don't wanna be the reason I'm unhappy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
而且成立新的天龙特攻队 应该会很好玩
Besides, it might be kind of fun to form the new A-Team.
嗨 林区太太 乔安娜进公司了吗？
Oh, hi, Mrs. Lynch. Is Joanna in already?
老天 你还没听说
Oh, my goodness. You haven't heard.
听说什么？
Heard what?
乔安娜昨晚过世了
Joanna passed away last night.
天啊 怎么会这样？
Oh, my God. How?
她下班出去时被计程车撞上
Well, she was leaving work, and she was hit by a cab.
天啊 我不敢相信
Oh, my God. Oh, I cannot believe it.
- 我知道   - 天啊…
- I know.     - Oh, God.
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
没想到你们两个这么好
I didn't realize that you were so close.
对 好到就差那么一点
Yes. So close.
林区太太 我知道这佃节骨眼 大家在情绪上都很煎熬
Mrs. Lynch, I know that this is an emotional and difficult time for all of us.
但在事发之前 乔安娜是不是正好有…
But by any chance, did Joanna send any paperwork your way...
把人事调动公文交给你？
...before it happened?
完全没有
No, nothing.
只盼当初 她晚个几秒钟过街就没事了
Imagine, if she'd just stepped off that curb a few seconds later...
对 差个几秒钟 她就还能跟我们在一起
Oh. Yes, yes, just a few seconds and she'd still be with us.
她没说到采购助理的事？
Nothing about an assistant buyer?
不好意思 我得走了
I'm sorry. I have to go.
早安
Good morning.
苏菲 我猜你还不知道 乔安娜的事
Oh, Sophie, I guess you didn't hear about Joanna.
我当然知道
I sure did.
我很兴奋能请到摩妮卡加入
I'm so excited about having Monica come onboard with us.
虽然开除艾米里欧主厨 让我觉得很过意不去
Although I do feel bad about having fired Chef Emilio.
那就像是失去了一个家人
It is like losing a member of the family.
不过对你们其中几位而言 真的是失去家人
Of course, that literally is the case for several of you.
东尼 卡洛斯 玛莉…
Tony, Carlos, Marie...
请向令尊转达 我们会有多想念艾米里欧
...please tell your father how much we're going to miss him.
我知道摩妮卡对这家店 有许多很棒的点子
Now, I know that Monica has a lot of great ideas for this place.
你们都看过她那篇评论了
Well, you all read the review. Ha, ha.
所以废话不多说
So without much further ado...
我在此向各位介绍本店的新主厨
...I present to you our new head chef.
我只想说只要有热忱
Um, I just wanna say, uh, that with a pinch of excitement...
肯吃苦 肯合作
...a dash of hard work, and a dollop of cooperation...
我们就能将本店的菜色…
...we can have the recipe...
你们打算杀我了我吗？
Are you going to kill me?